[
    {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "40 / 2",
        "choices": [10, 40, 20, 25],
        "correct": 20
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "30 / 2",
        "choices": [20, 10, 15, 13],
        "correct": 15
    },
    {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "80 / 10",
        "choices": [8, 9, 7, 12],
        "correct": 8
    },
    {
        "id": 4,
        "question": "40 / 4",
        "choices": [70, 15, 2, 10],
        "correct": 10
    },
    {
        "id": 5,
        "question": "90 / 3",
        "choices": [60, 70, 85, 30],
        "correct": 30
    },
    {
        "id": 6,
        "question": "140 / 2",
        "choices": [100, 20, 70, 80],
        "correct": 70
    },
    {
        "id": 7,
        "question": "300 / 3",
        "choices": [200, 100, 400, 300],
        "correct": 100
    },
    {
        "id": 8,
        "question": "1000 / 2",
        "choices": [500, 605, 800, 200],
        "correct": 500
    },
    {
        "id": 9,
        "question": "900/ 20 ",
        "choices": [45, 100, 80, 60],
        "correct": 45
    },
    {
        "id": 10,
        "question": "650 / 2",
        "choices": [11, 13, 12, 15],
        "correct": 13
    }
]